# **MOHAMED RINZAN FAZREEN**



An enthusiastic individual with 12 years of experience in sales and customer service seeking a suitable position in a fast-paced environment to demonstrate a remarkable difference in the corporate culture for the growth of the enterprise and career advancement. Successfully acquired overall experience in operations to handle distinguished position in medium and large organizations.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCES**

- ▶ Manager (Operations & Purchasing) | 2017 to 2021
  The Kids Warehouse/The Outlet Store/Cotton & Thread
- Assistant Manager | 2014 To 2017
   Qatar Duty Free Company (Qatar Airways)
- ➤ Senior Sales Supervisor | 2009 to 2014 Alshaya Company (Kuwait & UAE)

### **PROFESSIONAL QUALIFICATIONS**

- ► HND in Business Management

  Colombo Business College & Educational Academy.
- Customer Care Management Oxford College of Business.
- Diploma in Information Technology Turnkey IT Training Institute.
- Microsoft Windows & MS Office A & Q Graphics.



#### **PROFILE**

A hard working person who can work with less supervision and can handle tasks responsively. Ability to function in a multi-cultural working environment and multi task. Eagerly accepts new challenges and adapts well to any possible situation. Willing to shift to other professions and expertise in order to grow and learn other ventures.

#### CONTACTS

- 0507195825
- rinzanfazreen@gmail.com
- ♠ Dubai, United Arab Emirates

## **PERSONAL DETAILS**

Date of Birth: 10th August 1990

Age: 31 Years

Gender : Male

Marital Status : Married Nationality : Sri Lankan

Passport No: N5203473

Visa Status : Visit Visa

Diploma in English Institute of English.

Computer ProgrammingMYOWN Computer System Centre.

### **PROFESSIONAL SKILLS**

- ▶ Possess ability to work with a team and possess Leadership qualities.
- Ability to understand things as it is and to learn new theories and methods quickly.
- ► An excellent team member as an all-rounder.
- Creativity and great attention to detail.
- ► Flair for understanding organizations work culture and fast in adapting changes.
- An efficient multi-tasker.
- Excellent client relationship management.
- ► Equally effective working independently and in cooperation with others.

## **ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS**

► G.C.E (O/L) & G.C.E (A/L) Examination

Department of Examination in Sri Lanka 2006 & 2009

#### **DECLARATION**

► I hereby declare that the given information are true & correct to the best of my knowledge.

M. R. Fazreen

#### **AREAS OF EXPERTISE**

Strategic Sales Planning
Market Research & Analysis
Working with Key Decision makers
Profit Maximization
Forecasting

### **LANGUAGE SKILLS**



## **DRIVING LICENCE**

Sri Lanka : A021054208

Qatar: 29014410239